And Jarvis, wake up Daddy's song.
How's the app doing?
For the dashboard, give Claude code a reference image of what you want and it can pretty much
one-shot it.
Or you can design it in Claude design and build it out in Claude code.
This took me like five minutes to create.
Good evening sir.
Use voice mode to talk instead of type or connect it to Hermes agent to use their inbuilt voice
feature.
And if you want that British job, his voice connected to a fish audio.
Pulling up our app stats now.
Connect Claude or Hermes to Chrome so it has access to your browser.
Over the last seven days, we have 2,450 new downloads and generated 4,289 dollars in revenue.
Revenue cat MCP to track your app revenue.
For organic content, I'm still posting three short form videos a day.
Buffer or Metrical MCP to publish across all platforms in a single command.
On that, you spend $475 as a 1.5 return on that spend.
Use Meta's official ad MCP.
For other week, you see 16 customer emails.
Gmail MCP.
Organize all your FAQs into a mark down and Claude will take care of 90% of customer
service.
Since you already approved that direction, I handed it to Tom, the developer agent.
Define custom sub agents and equip them with proper skills and connectors.
Then your main agent can hand off work to the proper sub agent.
My recommendation today, review the backend PR, keep reading them into the screeches of
your ad angle and have scout research for the next set of organic content items to test.
What would you like me to handle first, sir?
Set this entire daily brief as a routine and Claude will have it ready for you the moment
You sit down to work.
Comment down if you want the full guide.